翻译、时间轴、压制：up主
Welcome to War Thunder Update 1.59: Flaming Arrows!
欢迎来到战争雷霆1.59版本更新：燃烧箭矢
Anti-tank guided missiles, a brand new hangar, new maps for ground vehicles and aircraft,
反坦克导弹 全新的机库 陆战和空战新地图
and of course, some fantastic new vehicles – you're sure to like it! Let's go!
当然还有一些极好的新载具——你一定会喜欢它 我们来看看吧
Anti-tank guided missiles, or ATGMs, are the star of the show in Update 1.59.
反坦克导弹 或称之为ATGM 是1.59更新中的重点
This new type of ordnance will fundamentally change the metagame in high-ranked ground battles.
这种新式武器将从根本上改变高级载具的战斗方式
ATGMs are missiles specifically designed to destroy enemy armored vehicles.
反坦克导弹是专门用来摧毁敌方的装甲车辆的
They can be guided using wires or a radio connection.
它们可以通过导线或无线电制导
Each tank-bearing nation in War Thunder has received a vehicle
战争雷霆中每个有坦克的国家都增加了反坦克导弹载具
equipped with ATGMs in the Flaming Arrows update. Here they are.
在燃烧箭矢的更新之后 他们来了
The USSR tech tree has received the IT-1, the first and sole missile tank with ATGMs
苏联科技树得到了IT-1 第一个专门用来搭载反坦克导弹的载具
accepted into actual military service.
而且在军队中服役过
The tank has no cannon, but has 15 powerful guided 'Drakon' missiles mounted on T-62 chassis.
该坦克没有炮 但在T-62的车身中装备了15枚强大的“龙”式反坦克导弹
The British are getting the Strv 81,
英国则拥有的Strv 81
a Swedish model of the Centurion 3, additionally armed with SS.11 missiles,
百夫长3的瑞典版本 装备了SS.11导弹
each of which can penetrate up to 600 mm of armor!
而该导弹的穿深高达600mm
Another tank in the game is receiving ATGMs as well – the German Raketejagdpanzer-2,
另一个游戏中的陆战科技树也得到了反坦克导弹——德国的Raketejagdpanzer-2（导弹式坦克歼击车2型）
an SPG based on the universally loved Jagdpanzer 4-5.
由广受好评的火炮式坦克歼击车4-5型改装而来
This vehicle has two ATGM launchers instead of a cannon.
这辆车有两个反坦克导弹发射器 而非装备一门火炮
Its ammunition complement of 14 deadly missiles is enough even for the most heated battles.
它那致命的导弹备弹量高达14枚 足够应对最激烈的战斗
Finally, the US will get the legendary Sheridan, a tank from the Vietnam War.
最后 美国将获得传奇般的谢里登 在越南战争中作战的坦克
The light and very maneuverable Sheridan is armed with a powerful 152 mm cannon,
又轻又<del>（跑得快）</del>具备高机动性的谢里登装备着强大的152mm<del>（神教）</del>火炮
which can fire both ordinary shells and guided missiles.
而这门炮既可发射普通的炮弹也可发射制导导弹
But what's that in the sky?
那么天上的<del>（大新闻）</del>载具呢
A winged dragon looks down from high on the new missile-equipped tank combat
在陆战中骑脸的翼龙装备着新火箭弹从天而降
the first turboprop aircraft in the game, the Westland Wyvern.
这是游戏中第一架涡轮螺旋桨飞机 韦斯特兰飞龙
This British heavy seaborne fighter carries an imposing armament of cannons,
这架英国海上重型战斗机携带着令人印象深刻的机炮
bombs and a staggering 16 aircraft rockets.
炸弹和高达16枚的火箭
Enough gifts for everyone – both tanks and aircraft.
这足够招待每个坦克和飞机了
And how its engine sings!
这引擎的声音也是特色之一
Soviet pilots are getting two fantastic vehicles.
苏联飞行员将获得两个极佳的载具
The Yak-30D is the long-awaited top-range fighter in the Yakovlev branch,
在雅科夫列夫科技树上 雅克-30D是期待已久的顶级战斗机
the fast, durable multi-purpose fighter interceptor.
高速 耐用的多用途战斗截击机
The USSR's fleet of heavy aircraft has been reinforced by the addition of the huge Tu-4,
图-4也将加入到苏联的重型飞机中
a Soviet copy of the American strategic B-29 Superfortress bomber,
尽管它是美国战略轰炸机B-29超级堡垒的苏联版山寨
only instead of machine guns, it has ten (ten!) 23mm cannons
却并不具备同样的机枪 它有着十门（十门！）23mm机炮
and a full 360-degree firing arms without dead-zones.
并且这些武器可以进行360度无死角射击
Incidentally, the B-29 itself has received an updated in-game model, and now looks amazingly beautiful.
顺便说一句 B-29自身也更新了模型 现在看起来美得令人惊讶
The most extraordinary addition in this update is the German Heinkel 219 night fighter,
德国亨克尔219夜间战斗机是本次更新中最出彩的部分
not only because it's a truly excellent aircraft with fine maneuverability and six cannons.
不仅因为它具有不错的机动性和六门机炮
This aircraft's model was created by a War Thunder player, someone just like you.
而是因为它由和你差不多的战争雷霆玩家制作
We accepted this model as part of our revenue share program,
我们认同这种模式作为我们收入分享计划的一部分
and now a portion of the revenue from each purchase of the He 219 will go to the model's author.
每笔He 219的收入都会有一部分分享给这个模型的作者
Don't just sit there, learn 3D editing and make money from your favourite game!
别总是坐在那儿玩 学习3D制作并从你喜爱的游戏中赚钱
Now back to the ground.
现在回到陆战
Tanks with ATGMs are far from the extent of the new additions to our armored vehicles in War Thunder 1.59.
战争雷霆1.59版本中不仅加入了装备反坦克导弹的陆战载具
The massive T29 tank with its impressive turret armor will be arriving in the hangars of American tankers.
拥有着令人印象深刻的炮塔装甲的巨大的T29坦克将会加入到美国陆战玩家的车库当中
The LVT(A)(1) amphibious landing vehicle is a fun tank that floats,
LVT（A）（1）两栖登陆坦克则是一辆能漂在水上的<del>（赛艇）</del>坦克
with its two extra machine guns at the rear, it arrives as a new American reserve machine.
它后面还有两挺机枪 会作为新的美系初始载具登场
Germany has also received a new reserve tank – an early modification of the Panzer III,
德国也获得了新的初始载具——一辆三号坦克的早期版本
the model B(PzKpfw. III Ausf. B.)
B型（三号坦克B型）
The new Sturer Emil German SPG with a 128 mm calibre sniper cannon
德国的新自行火炮斯图尔·埃米尔有着128毫米口径的反坦克炮
and an open cabin will continue the line of new additions from the last update
作为敞篷车将会继续加入到上次更新后的敞篷坦歼线当中
the Dicker Max and Nashorn SPGs.
即自行火炮大麦克斯和犀牛所在的科技树
Additionally, Germany has received captured KV-2 and T-34 tanks, which is awesome!
不仅如此 德国得到了缴获版的KV-2和T-34坦克 着实不错
The British tree has gained a new modification of the Cromwell tank with unguided rockets.
英国科技树则获得了一个装备着非制导火箭的新版克伦威尔坦克
Exactly the same rockets that are used on the Hurricane fighter,
和飓风战斗机使用的火箭弹相同
but they're a lot easier to fire from a tank!
不过在坦克上使用就容易多了
For Soviet tankers – two nimble and stubby air portable SPGs, the ASU-57 and the ASU-85,
而对于苏联坦克玩家们 他们获得了两辆短小精悍的空降自行火炮ASU-57和ASU-85，
both with excellent cannons.
均具有优良的火炮
A new version of the KV-2 armed with the ZiS-6 cannon has also arrived.
而装备着ZIS-6火炮的KV-2新版本也到来了
This cannon is powerful and accurate, capable of landing solid shots over great distances.
该火炮精度不错且威力强大 足够在远距离上精确地给予敌人以沉重的打击
The sniper KV-2 – you've never seen anything like it!
<del>（黑孙子）</del>狙击手KV-2——你从未见过这样的东西
All these new vehicles need a new hangar!
所有这些新的载具需要新的机库
We've completely revamped the hangar's design,
我们完全改变了机库的设计
and now tanks, SPGs and other armored vehicles prepare for battle in a repair shop
现在坦克 自行火炮和其他装甲车辆将在<del>（工房）</del>维修工厂准备战斗
under an open sky, and aircraft have their own spacious hangar and landing strip.
飞机也会拥有自己的宽敞的露天机库和跑道
We continue to make new locations and missions.
我们还持续地制作着新的地图和任务
We're pleased to present a new map for mixed battles – Novorossiysk.
我们很高兴能带来混合战新地图——新罗西斯克
There, in the autumn of 1943,
还有在1943年秋季
a Soviet landing party freed the strategically important Black Sea port from its occupants
苏联登陆部队从侵略者中解放出来的具有重要战略意义的黑海港口
in a unique operation, which laid the groundwork for the liberation of southern USSR.
这次特别的行动为苏联南部的解放奠定了基础
This summer, we invite War Thunder pilots and tankers to fight for the port of Novorossiysk.
今年夏天 我们有请战争雷霆的空战和陆战玩家为新罗西斯克港而战
Fierce skirmishes for the railroad terminal and city park will unfold here,
激烈的小规模战斗将在火车站和城市公园中展开
amid ruined bombed-out buildings and derailed train cars.
其中有着被炸毁的建筑物和脱轨的列车车厢
Great news for pilots – we've expanded the size of the Britain map fourfold.
给飞行员们的好消息——我们已经将英国地图扩大到原来的四倍
A large part of the English Channel and part of France is now available in the map.
绝大部分的英吉利海峡和一部分法国领土被划入了地图
A new mission on the updated 128 by 128 kilometer map
新的任务将在这个更新后的128kmX128km的地图上产生
is dedicated to an operation to evacuate French troops from the port of Boulogne-sur-Mer
是一个专门帮助法国军队从滨海布洛涅港撤退的行动
a whole new battle awaits you there!
一个全新的战斗等待着你
We can't tell you about all the new additions in War Thunder: Flaming Arrows in one short video
战争雷霆：燃烧箭矢的所有新特性不可能在一个简短的视频中讲完
updated models for ground vehicles and aircraft, numerous bugfixes and improvements,
陆战和空战的载具新模型 大量的修正和改进
and new additions to flight models and missions.
还有新增加的空战载具和任务
Read the full changelog on our official site - link in the description bellow.
阅读我们官网的完整更新报告——链接在下方简介处
subscribe to our Youtube channel and don't forget to keep up with our news on social networks!
订阅我们Youtube的频道 别忘了跟进我们在社交网络上发布的消息
Victory will be ours!
胜利是属于我们的
See you on the battlefields of War Thunder!
在战争雷霆的战场上再见